[{"answer": "my friend and my friend..", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Three inmates, five guards and a shrink all in one years' time", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah.  My old man beat the tar out of me", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You gotta be kidding", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm even talkin' hellholes where the warden's hard as a bar of iron.  No one wants these assholes behind their walls, dealing with 'e", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Day out", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Who's that", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " my friend!  That TV scumbag", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Technically, mass murderer", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Y'ever do one on my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How 'bout my friend", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, it's pretty hard to beat the king", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He squashed him mentally before physically defeating him", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend and my friend have that edge", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why can't they just shake hands and be friends", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Obviously they made the first move", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Never is a very long time, my friend.  A word only the weak use.  I'm not a sore loser.  Even if I don't have a leg to stand on, I'm going to get up and fight this world until I'm on top again", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And that's the way of the world", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Just for fun, I guess", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend stops sawin' on my leg and says,", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well do you believe you have any choice when it's time for you to die", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You know what this has to do with Grace Mulberry?  I'll tell ya what it has to do with Grace Mulberry.  ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " The next to last victim.  The one whose grandson testified at the trial that his grandfather was trying to help you..", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He saw what", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "He saw it..", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The Demon...He saw the Demon", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, riddle me this my friend.  How do you feel about the fact that you're never gonna see my friend again", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Says the that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " When have they ever been right", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Was what worth it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Take a wild stab", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "The entire wing", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That's my opinion", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "There's gonna be hell to pay", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Probably not, but we're gonna give it the old college try", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Exciting, isn't it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Right out the front door", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It  happening", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I wondered how long it would be before we'd get to be alone together.  And I wondered if I could wait that long", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "We had nothing to do with that riot.  That riot was just", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No. Not really.  You're scum my friend.  You did it for ratings.  You poured gasoline on the fire. You didn't give a shit about us or about anything my friend except yourself.  That's why nobody really gives a shit about you my friend. That's why they didn't deploy helicoptors", "docId": "natural-born-killers_shoot.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What about him", "qsentId": 42}]